<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Adam Sandler[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/19292</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/tv9V6QsuZ3bcp4ciUJjwjcc4qAg.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Adam Sandler was born on September 9, 1966, in Brooklyn, New York, to Judy and Stanley Sandler. At 17, he took his first step towards becoming a stand-up comedian when he spontaneously took the stage at a Boston comedy club. He found he was a natural comic. He nurtured his talent while at New York University (graduating with a Bachelor of Fine Arts degree in 1991) by performing regularly in clubs and at universities. During his freshman year, he snagged a recurring role as the Huxtable family's friend Smitty on "The Cosby Show" (1984). While working at a comedy club in L.A., he was "discovered" by Dennis Miller, who recommended him to "Saturday Night Live" (1975) producer Lorne Michaels and told him that Sandler had a big talent. This led to his being cast in the show in 1990, which he also wrote for in addition to performing. After "Saturday Night Live" (1975), Sandler went on to the movies, starring in such hit comedies as Airheads (1994), Happy Gilmore (1996), Billy Madison (1995) and Big Daddy (1999/I). He has also starred in Mr. Deeds (2002) alongside Winona Ryder; Eight Crazy Nights (2002), an animated movie about the Jewish festival of Chanukah; and Punch-Drunk Love (2002). He also writes and produces many of his own films and has composed songs for several of them, including The Wedding Singer (1998). Sandler has had several of his songs placed on the "Billboard" charts, including the classic "The Chanukah Song".</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Al Pacino[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/1158</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/ks7Ba8x9fJUlP9decBr6Dh5mThX.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Alfredo James "Al" Pacino (born April 25, 1940) is an American film and stage actor and director. He is famous for playing mobsters, including Michael Corleone in The Godfather trilogy, Tony Montana in Scarface, Alphonse "Big Boy" Caprice in Dick Tracy and Carlito Brigante in Carlito's Way, though he has also appeared several times on the other side of the law — as a police officer, detective and a lawyer. His role as Frank Slade in Scent of a Woman won him the Academy Award for Best Actor in 1992 after receiving seven previous Oscar nominations.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Anthony Hopkins[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/4173</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/jdoBTIru71FbPuHGEgox5RVmIO0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Anthony Hopkins was born on 31 December 1937, in Margam, Glamorgan, Wales. Influenced by Richard Burton, he decided to study at College of Music and Drama in Cardiff and graduated in 1957. In 1965, he moved to London and joined the National Theatre, invited by Laurence Olivier, who could see the talent in Hopkins. In 1967, he made his first film for television, A Flea in Her Ear (1967) (TV).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Anthony Quinn[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/5401</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/9sKpm4KCoUbmMbR86fpqcgBCHrJ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Anthony Quinn (April 21, 1915 – June 3, 2001) was a Mexican-American actor, as well as a painter and writer. He starred in numerous critically acclaimed and commercially successful films, including Zorba the Greek, Lawrence of Arabia, The Guns of Navarone, The Message , " Lion of the Desert" and Federico Fellini's La strada. He won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor twice; for Viva Zapata! in 1952 and Lust for Life in 1956.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Arnold Schwarzenegger[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/1100</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/zooXFWF1JtrV7UnZyGRxXDW11qt.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Arnold Alois Schwarzenegger (born July 30, 1947) is an Austrian-American former professional bodybuilder, actor, model, businessman and politician who served as the 38th Governor of California (2003–2011).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Ben Affleck[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/880</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/7Zy12dUasr43oF8hyU5iBz5iOpO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Ben Affleck (born Benjamin Géza Affleck-Boldt; August 15, 1972) is an American actor, film director, writer, and producer. He became known in the mid-1990s with his performance in the Kevin Smith films Mallrats (1995) and Chasing Amy (1997). Affleck is an Academy Award as well as a Golden Globe Award winner, along with Matt Damon, for their collaborative screenplay for the 1997 film Good Will Hunting. He established himself as a Hollywood leading man, having starred in several big budget films, such as Armageddon (1998), Pearl Harbor (2001), Changing Lanes (2002), The Sum of All Fears (2002), and Daredevil (2003).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Ben Stiller[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/7399</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/o9M2PyoF7QDSMq1OwW0D892fIkV.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>​Benjamin Edward "Ben" Stiller (born November 30, 1965) is an American comedian, actor, writer, film director, and producer. He is the son of veteran comedians and actors Jerry Stiller and Anne Meara. After beginning his acting career with a play, Stiller wrote several mockumentaries, and was offered two of his own shows, both entitled The Ben Stiller Show. He began acting in films, and had his directorial debut with Reality Bites. Throughout his career he has since written, starred in, directed, and/or produced over 50 films including Heavyweights, There's Something About Mary, Meet the Parents, Zoolander, Dodgeball, and Tropic Thunder. In addition, he has had multiple cameos in music videos, television shows, and films. Stiller is a member of the comedic acting brotherhood colloquially known as the Frat Pack. His films have grossed more than $2.1 billion domestically (United States and Canada), with an average of $73 million per film. Throughout his career, he has received several awards and honors including an Emmy Award, several MTV Movie Awards, and a Teen Choice Award.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Brad Pitt[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/287</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/kU3B75TyRiCgE270EyZnHjfivoq.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>William Bradley "Brad" Pitt (born December 18, 1963) is an American actor and film producer. Pitt has received two Academy Award nominations and four Golden Globe Award nominations, winning one. He has been described as one of the world's most attractive men, a label for which he has received substantial media attention. Pitt began his acting career with television guest appearances, including a role on the CBS prime-time soap opera Dallas in 1987. He later gained recognition as the cowboy hitchhiker who seduces Geena Davis's character in the 1991 road movie Thelma & Louise. Pitt's first leading roles in big-budget productions came with A River Runs Through It (1992) and Interview with the Vampire (1994). He was cast opposite Anthony Hopkins in the 1994 drama Legends of the Fall, which earned him his first Golden Globe nomination. In 1995 he gave critically acclaimed performances in the crime thriller Seven and the science fiction film 12 Monkeys, the latter securing him a Golden Globe Award for Best Supporting Actor and an Academy Award nomination.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Bradley Cooper[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/51329</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/z5LUl9bljJnah3S5rtN7rScrmI8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Bradley Cooper (born January 5, 1975) is an American film, theater, and television actor. He is known for his roles as Will Tippin in the TV series Alias, Phil Wenneck in the 2009 film The Hangover (and its sequels), and Templeton "Faceman" Peck in 2010 movie The A-Team.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Christian Bale[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/3894</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/2ocrTd8ChuUyJOzMuD4PsQw8eCB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Christian Charles Philip Bale is a Welsh-born English actor. In addition to starring roles in big budget Hollywood films, he has long been heavily involved in films produced by independent producers and art houses. Bale first caught the public eye when he was cast in the starring role of Steven Spielberg's Empire of the Sun at the age of 13, playing an English boy who is separated from his parents and subsequently finds himself lost in a Japanese internment camp during World War II. Since then, he has portrayed a wide range of characters. Bale is especially noted for his cult following: the tenth anniversary issue of Entertainment Weekly hailed him as one of the "Top 8 Most Powerful Cult Figures of the Past Decade", citing his cult status on the Internet. EW called Bale one of the "Most Creative People in Entertainment" in anticipation of the release American Psycho (2000). The Guardian named Bale as one of the best actors never to have received an Academy Award nomination.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Client Eastwood[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/190</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/n8h4ZHteFFXfmzUW6OEaPWanDnm.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Clinton "Clint" Eastwood, Jr. (born May 31, 1930) is an American film actor, director, producer, composer and politician. Following his breakthrough role on the TV series Rawhide (1959–65), Eastwood starred as the Man with No Name in Sergio Leone's Dollars Trilogy of spaghetti westerns (A Fistful of Dollars, For a Few Dollars More, and The Good, the Bad and the Ugly) in the 1960s, and as San Francisco Police Department Inspector Harry Callahan in the Dirty Harry films (Dirty Harry, Magnum Force, The Enforcer, Sudden Impact, and The Dead Pool) during the 1970s and 1980s. These roles, along with several others in which he plays tough-talking no-nonsense police officers, have made him an enduring cultural icon of masculinity.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Denzel Washington[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/5292</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/khMf8LLTtppUwuZqqnigD2nAy26.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Denzel Hayes Washington, Jr. (born December 28, 1954) is an American actor, screenwriter, director and film producer. He first rose to prominence when he joined the cast of the medical drama St. Elsewhere, playing Dr. Philip Chandler for six years. He has received much critical acclaim for his work in film since the 1990s, including for his portrayals of real-life figures, such as Steve Biko, Malcolm X, Rubin "Hurricane" Carter, Melvin B. Tolson, Frank Lucas, and Herman Boone.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Dustin Hoffman[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/4483</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/3pZx8NB30KIw31rBAT62TUDQFEb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Dustin Hoffman is an American stage, film and television actor. After versatile portrayals of antiheroes and vulnerable types of characters in stage plays, he had his breakthrough film role as Benjamin Braddock in the feature film "The Graduate". Since then he starred in many films, like "Papillon", "Kramer vs. Kramer", "Tootsie", and "Rain Man". He has won two Academy Awards, five Golden Globes, three BAFTAs, three Drama Desk Awards, a Genie Award, and an Emmy Award - and received the AFI Life Achievement Award in 1999.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Eddie Murphy[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/776</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/bsi706zdqs0KAPdOsqz6AkLNcFF.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Edward "Eddie" Regan Murphy (born April 3, 1961) is an American actor, voice actor, film director, producer, comedian and singer.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Harrison Ford[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/3</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/7LOTdRfHU1H1qHBxpUv3jT04eWB.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Legendary Hollywood Icon Harrison Ford was born on July 13, 1942 in Chicago, Illinois.  His family history includes a strong lineage of actors, radio personalities, and models.  Harrison attended public high school in Park Ridge, Illinois where he was a member of the school Radio Station WMTH. Harrison worked as the lead voice for sports reporting at WMTH for several years.  Acting wasn’t a major interest to Ford until his junior year at Ripon College when he first took an acting class. Harrison Ford’s career started in 1964 when he travelled to California in search of a voice-over job. He never received that position, but instead signed a contract with Columbia Pictures where he earned $150 weekly to play small fill in roles in various films.  Through the 60’s Harrison worked on several TV shows including Gunsmoke, Ironside, Kung Fu, and American Style.  It wasn’t until 1967 that Harrison received his first credited role in the Western film, A Time for Killing. Dissatisfied with the meager roles he was being offered, Ford took a hiatus from acting to work as a self-employed carpenter. This seemingly odd diversion turned out to be a blessing in disguise for Harrison’s acting career when he was soon hired by famous film producer George Lucas.  This was a turning point in Harrison’s life that led to him be casted in milestone roles such as Hans Solo and Indiana Jones.  Since his most famous roles in the Star Wars Trilogy and Raiders of the Lost Ark, Harrison Ford has starred in over 40 films.  Many criticize his recent work, saying his performances have been lackluster leading to commercially disappointing films. Harrison has always worked hard to protect his off-screen private life, keeping details about his children and marriages quite.  He has a total of five children including one recent adoption with third and current wife Calista Flockhart. In addition to acting Harrison Ford is passionate about environmental conservation, aviation, and archeology.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Jack Nicholson[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/514</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/hINAkm21g80UbaAxA6rHhOaT5Jk.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>John Joseph "Jack" Nicholson (born April 22, 1937) is an American actor, film director, producer and writer. He is renowned for his often dark-themed portrayals of neurotic characters. Nicholson has been nominated for Academy Awards 12 times. He has won the Academy Award for Best Actor twice, for One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest and for As Good as It Gets. He won the Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for the 1983 film Terms of Endearment. He is tied with Walter Brennan for most acting wins by a male actor (three), and second to Katharine Hepburn for most acting wins overall (four).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Jason Statham[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/976</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/PhWiWgasncGWD9LdbsGcmxkV4r.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Jason Statham (born 26. July 1967) is an English actor and martial artist, known for his roles in the Guy Ritchie crime films Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels; Revolver; and Snatch.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Jim Carrey[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/206</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/a46mhZ3ZLIx3SOGTj3WhchC7XbQ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>James Eugene "Jim" Carrey is a Canadian-American actor, comedian, singer and writer. He has received two Golden Globe Awards and has also been nominated on four occasions.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Joe Pesci[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/4517</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/2CaYAhUZgkAeqtpIzuqGcqArsOy.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Joseph Frank "Joe" Pesci (born February 9, 1943) is an American actor, comedian, singer and musician. He is known for his roles as violent mobsters, funnymen, comic foils and quirky sidekicks. Pesci has starred in a number of high profile films such as Goodfellas, Casino, Raging Bull, Once Upon a Time in America, My Cousin Vinny, Easy Money, JFK, Moonwalker, Home Alone, Home Alone 2: Lost in New York, and the 2nd, 3rd, and 4th Lethal Weapon films.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Johnny Depp[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/85</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/ea4fTp9T8Zy2KWxyFsqDIBgHZmb.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>John Christopher "Johnny" Depp II (born June 9, 1963) is an American actor and musician. He has won the Golden Globe Award and Screen Actors Guild award for Best Actor.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Keanu Reeves[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/6384</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/bOlYWhVuOiU6azC4Bw6zlXZ5QTC.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Keanu Charles Reeves is a Canadian actor. Reeves is known for his roles in Bill & Ted's Excellent Adventure, Speed, Point Break, and The Matrix trilogy as Neo. He has collaborated with major directors such as Stephen Frears (in the 1988 period drama Dangerous Liaisons); Gus Van Sant (in the 1991 independent film My Own Private Idaho); and Bernardo Bertolucci (in the 1993 film Little Buddha). Referring to his 1991 film releases, The New York Times' critic, Janet Maslin, praised Reeves' versatility, saying that he "displays considerable discipline and range. He moves easily between the buttoned-down demeanor that suits a police procedural story and the loose-jointed manner of his comic roles." A repeated theme in roles he has portrayed is that of saving the world, including the characters of Ted Logan, Buddha, Neo, Johnny Mnemonic, John Constantine and Klaatu.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Kevin Costner[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/1269</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/ePo87kGyyY8JZ3z7Zm7Z2GYdmJ8.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Kevin Michael Costner (born January 18, 1955) is an American actor, singer, musician, producer, director, and businessman. He has been nominated for three BAFTA (British Academy of Film and Television Arts) Awards, won two Academy Awards, and two Golden Globe Awards. Costner's roles include Lt. John J. Dunbar in the film Dances with Wolves, Jim Garrison in JFK, Ray Kinsella in Field of Dreams, Robin Hood in Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves, Crash Davis in Bull Durham, Robert "Butch" Haynes in A Perfect World and Eliot Ness in The Untouchables. Costner also founded the band Modern West, and has performed with the band since 2007. [CR]Description above from the Wikipedia article Kevin Costner, licensed under CC-BY-SA, full list of contributors on Wikipedia</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Kevin Spacey[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/1979</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/x7wF050iuCASefLLG75s2uDPFUu.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Kevin Spacey Fowler (born July 26, 1959), better known by his stage name Kevin Spacey, is an American actor of screen and stage, film director, producer, screenwriter and singer who has resided in the United Kingdom since 2003. He began his career as a stage actor during the 1980s before obtaining supporting roles in film and television. He gained critical acclaim in the early 1990s that culminated in his first Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor for the neo-noir crime thriller The Usual Suspects (1995), and an Academy Award for Best Actor for midlife crisis-themed drama American Beauty (1999).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Kurt Russell[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/6856</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/rlnFuNkisPpuypARI7QaGCmOY6V.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Kurt Vogel Russell (born March 17, 1951) is an American television and film actor. His first acting roles were as a child in television series, including a lead role in the Western series The Travels of Jaimie McPheeters (1963–1964). In the 1970s, he signed a ten-year contract with the Walt Disney Company, where he became, according to Robert Osborne, the "studio's top star of the '70s". In 1979, Russell was nominated for an Emmy Award for the made-for-television film Elvis.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Liam Neeson[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/3896</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/9mdAohLsDu36WaXV2N3SQ388bvz.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>William John "Liam" Neeson OBE (born 7 June 1952) is an Irish actor who has been nominated for an Oscar, a BAFTA and three Golden Globe Awards.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Matt Damon[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/1892</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/elSlNgV8xVifsbHpFsqrPGxJToZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Matthew Paige "Matt" Damon (born October 8, 1970) is an American actor, screenwriter, and philanthropist.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Mel Gibson[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2461</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/6VGgL0bBvPIJ9vDOyyGf5nK2zL4.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Mel Colm-Cille Gerard Gibson, AO (born January 3, 1956) is an actor, film director, producer and screenwriter. Born in Peekskill, New York, Gibson moved with his parents to Sydney, Australia when he was 12 years old and later studied acting at the Australian National Institute of Dramatic Art. After appearing in the Mad Max and Lethal Weapon series, Gibson went on to direct and star in the Academy Award-winning Braveheart. In 2004, he directed and produced The Passion of the Christ, a controversial, yet successful, film portraying the last hours in the life of Jesus Christ. Outside his career, remarks by Gibson have generated accusations of homophobia, antisemitism, racism, and misogyny; he has previously attributed the statements to his alcoholism.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Michael Caine[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/3895</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/vvj0JMSFpOajXCE46Hy4dyqSP2U.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Sir Michael Caine is an English film actor. He became known for several notable critically acclaimed performances, particularly in films such as Zulu (1964), The Italian Job (1969), Get Carter (1971), Educating Rita (1983) and more recently Batman Begins and The Dark Knight. Caine was knighted in 2000 by Queen Elizabeth II, in recognition of his contribution to cinema.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Mickey Rourke[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2295</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/AvGzQ8fvjurGmZW3W1wlQ5WfSeT.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Philip Andre "Mickey" Rourke, Jr. (born September 16, 1952) is an American actor and screenwriter who has appeared primarily as a leading man in action, drama, and thriller films.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Morgan Freeman[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/192</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/oGJQhOpT8S1M56tvSsbEBePV5O1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Morgan Porterfield Freeman, Jr. is an American actor, film director, and narrator. He is noted for his reserved demeanor and authoritative speaking voice. Freeman has received Academy Award nominations for his performances in Street Smart, Driving Miss Daisy, The Shawshank Redemption and Invictus and won in 2005 for Million Dollar Baby. He has also won a Golden Globe Award and a Screen Actors Guild Award.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Nicolas Cage[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2963</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/fW37Gbk5PJZuXvyZwtcr0cMwPKY.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Nicolas Kim Coppola (born January 7, 1964), known professionally as Nicolas Cage, is an American actor, producer and director. He has performed in leading roles in a variety of films, ranging from romantic comedies and dramas to science fiction and action movies. Cage is known for his prolificacy, appearing in at least one film per year, nearly every year since 1980 (with the exception of 1985 and 1991).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Owen Wilson[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/887</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/j7oYgvfDiO34VcFdSB7GhM2CSle.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Owen Cunningham Wilson (born November 18, 1968) is an American actor and screenwriter from Dallas, Texas. His older brother, Andrew and younger brother, Luke, are also actors. He has had a long association with filmmaker Wes Anderson, having shared co-writing and acting credits for Bottle Rocket (1996) and The Royal Tenenbaums (2001), which was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Original Screenplay, and for his collaborations with fellow actor Ben Stiller. The two have appeared in ten films together.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Pierce Brosnan[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/517</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/1JXL0zrA26JjdoX8sqf57fJRDVM.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Pierce Brendan Brosnan, OBE (16 May 1953) is an Irish actor, film producer and environmentalist who holds Irish and American citizenship.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Robert Carlyle[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/18023</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/dLNeFPfJACiCiUz3oEdAjeKIwvZ.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Robert Carlyle, OBE (born 14 April 1961) is a Scottish film and television actor. He is known for a variety of roles including those in Trainspotting, Hamish Macbeth, The Full Monty, The World Is Not Enough, Angela's Ashes, The 51st State, and 28 Weeks Later. He also portrayed Doctor Nicholas Rush in Stargate Universe.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Robert De Niro[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/380</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/lvTSwUcvJRLAJ2FB5qFaukel516.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Robert De Niro, Jr. (born August 17, 1943) is an American actor, director, and producer.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Robert Downey Jr[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/3223</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/1YjdSym1jTG7xjHSI0yGGWEsw5i.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Robert John Downey, Jr. (born April 4, 1965) is an American actor. Downey made his screen debut in 1970, at the age of five, when he appeared in his father's film Pound, and has worked consistently in film and television ever since. During the 1980s he had roles in a series of coming of age films associated with the Brat Pack. Less Than Zero (1987) is particularly notable, not only because it was the first time Downey's acting would be acknowledged by critics, but also because the role pushed Downey's already existing drug habit one step further. After Zero, Downey started landing roles in bigger films such as Air America (1990), Soapdish (1991) and Natural Born Killers (1994). He played Charlie Chaplin in the 1992 film Chaplin, for which he received an Academy Award nomination for Best Actor.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Robin Williams[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2157</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/5KebSMXT8uj2D0gkaMFJ8VEp53.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Robin McLaurin Williams (July 21, 1951 – August 11, 2014) was an American actor and stand-up comedian. Rising to fame with his role as the alien Mork in the TV series Mork & Mindy (1978–1982), Williams went on to establish a successful career in both stand-up comedy and feature film acting. His film career included such acclaimed films as "The World According to Garp" (1982), Good Morning, Vietnam (1987), Dead Poets Society (1989), Awakenings (1990), The Fisher King (1991), and Good Will Hunting (1997), as well as financial successes such as Popeye (1980), Hook (1991), Aladdin (1992), Mrs. Doubtfire (1993), Jumanji (1995), The Birdcage (1996), Night at the Museum (2006), and Happy Feet (2006).</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Russell Crowe[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/934</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/ktuOAyUHM2u2YPPChH8gAArxJ7b.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Russell Ira Crowe (born 7 April 1964) is a New Zealand-born Australian actor and musician. His acting career began in the late 1980s with roles in Australian television series including Police Rescue and Neighbours. In the early 1990s, Crowe's local prominence peaked when he won the Australian Film Industry Award for Best Actor for his portrayal of an inner-city skinhead in the Geoffrey Wright film, Romper Stomper. In the late 1990s, Crowe transferred his acting ambitions to the USA with his breakout role in L.A. Confidential (1997). Crowe won the Academy Award for Best Actor for Gladiator in 2001 and has received three Academy Award nominations for Best Actor in a Leading Role: The Insider (1999), Gladiator (2000) and A Beautiful Mind (2001). He is also co-owner of National Rugby League team the South Sydney Rabbitohs.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Ryan Reynolds[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/10859</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/h1co81QaT2nJA41Sb7eZwmWl1L2.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Ryan Rodney Reynolds (born October 23, 1976) is a Canadian actor. He portrayed Michael Bergen on the ABC sitcom Two Guys and a Girl (1998–2001), Billy Simpson in the YTV Canadian teen soap opera Hillside (1991), as well as Marvel Comics characters Hannibal King in Blade: Trinity (2004), Wade Wilson / Weapon XI in X-Men Origins: Wolverine (2009), and the title character in Deadpool (2016) for which he received a Golden Globe Award nomination.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Samuel L. Jackson[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2231</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/dlW6prW9HwYDsIRXNoFYtyHpSny.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Samuel Leroy Jackson (born December 21, 1948) is an American film and television actor and film producer. After Jackson became involved with the Civil Rights Movement, he moved on to acting in theater at Morehouse College, and then films. He had several small roles such as in the film Goodfellas, Def by Temptation, before meeting his mentor, Morgan Freeman, and the director Spike Lee. After gaining critical acclaim for his role in Jungle Fever in 1991, he appeared in films such as Patriot Games, Amos & Andrew, True Romance and Jurassic Park. In 1994 he was cast as Jules Winnfield in Pulp Fiction, and his performance received several award nominations and critical acclaim</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Sean Bean[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/48</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/iIxP2IzvcLgr5WaTBD4UfSqaV3q.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Shaun Mark "Sean" Bean (born 17 April 1959) is an English film and stage actor. Bean is best known for starring roles in the films Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring, GoldenEye, Patriot Games, Troy, National Treasure and Silent Hill, as well as the television series Sharpe. Bean has also acted in a number of television productions, most recent being HBO's Game of Thrones, as well as performing voice work for computer games and television adverts.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Seth Rogen[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/19274</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/aQc8O52P4vWDRfuxCLsz9rvnwf3.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Seth Rogen (born April 15, 1982) is a Canadian actor, comedian, voice artist, screenwriter, and film producer. Rogen began his career doing stand-up comedy for four years during his teens, coming in second place in the Vancouver Amateur Comedy Contest in 1998. While still living in his native Vancouver, he landed a supporting role in Freaks and Geeks. Shortly after Rogen moved to Los Angeles for his role, Freaks and Geeks was canceled after one season due to poor ratings. He then got a part on the equally short-lived Undeclared, which also hired him as a staff writer. After landing a job as a staff writer on the final season of Da Ali G Show, for which Rogen and the other writers received an Emmy nomination, he was guided by film producer Judd Apatow toward a film career. Rogen was cast in a major supporting role and credited as a co-producer in Apatow's directorial debut, The 40-Year-Old Virgin. </summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Sylvester Stallone[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/16483</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/gnmwOa46C2TP35N7ARSzboTdx2u.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Sylvester Stallone Gardenzio, nicknamed Sly, (New York, July 6, 1946), is an actor, screenwriter, director, film producer and American entrepreneur.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Tom Cruise[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/500</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/3oWEuo0e8Nx8JvkqYCDec2iMY6K.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Thomas "Tom" Cruise (born Thomas Cruise Mapother IV; July 3, 1962) is an American actor and filmmaker. He has been nominated for three Academy Awards and has won three Golden Globe Awards.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Tom Hanks[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/31</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/pQFoyx7rp09CJTAb932F2g8Nlho.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Thomas Jeffrey "Tom" Hanks (born July 9, 1956) is an American actor, producer, writer and director. Hanks worked in television and family-friendly comedies, gaining wide notice in 1988's Big, before achieving success as a dramatic actor in several notable roles, including Andrew Beckett in Philadelphia, the title role in Forrest Gump, Commander James A. Lovell in Apollo 13, Captain John H. Miller in Saving Private Ryan, Joe Fox in You've Got Mail and Chuck Noland in Cast Away. Hanks won consecutive Best Actor Academy Awards, in 1993 for Philadelphia and in 1994 for Forrest Gump. U.S. domestic box office totals for his films exceed $3.9 billion.</summary>
</dir>
<dir>
	<title>[B][COLORwhite]Tommy Lee Jones[/COLOR][/B]</title>
	<tmdb>person/movies/2176</tmdb>
	<thumbnail>https://image.tmdb.org/t/p/w600_and_h900_bestv2/gRXugLFvr1oHZ6alLUxmYDq8cgW.jpg</thumbnail>
	<summary>Tommy Lee Jones (born September 15, 1946) is an American actor and film director.</summary>
</dir>

